<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Makeroni</title>
    <link>https://makeroni.cc/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Makeroni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 13:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://makeroni.cc/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TS80P Soldering Iron</title>
      <link>https://makeroni.cc/review/ts80p-soldering-iron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 13:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makeroni.cc/review/ts80p-soldering-iron/</guid>
      <description>DJ reviews the TS80P Soldering Iron
I&amp;rsquo;ve been through most of the TS range of soldering irons, the original TS100 was a solid performer, mostly limited by its power supply. The OLED display and the microcontroller driven internals offered up so many possibilities for smarter soldering. Many of which would be unrealised until folks started hacking their own firmware for the device. It was super compact though and created a new space for compact smart soldering irons for the maker toolbag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>https://makeroni.cc/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 14:28:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makeroni.cc/review/</guid>
      <description>Makeroni reviews are short reviews from the Makeroni members about tools, kits, or anything else they have found useful in their Making experience. Anyone at Makeroni can submit a review for the site - It&amp;rsquo;s one of the easiest ways to contribute to Makeroni. Just ping Codepope on the Makeroni Discord or drop a mail to Makeroni with your review or questions and we&amp;rsquo;ll get you published here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Power Bank Keep Alive</title>
      <link>https://makeroni.cc/review/smart-power-bank-keep-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 14:28:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://makeroni.cc/review/smart-power-bank-keep-alive/</guid>
      <description>Marian reviews the Smart Power Back Keep Alive
I bought this one, and am very pleased with it. Does what it says it does. It also comes with a note which explains there&amp;rsquo;s a screw on the device which acts as a potentiometer so that you can adjust the current to the absolute lowest you need. For under a tenner, great!
Want your review featured on Makeroni? Ping Codepope on the Discord server!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
